▍2026 美网 女单决赛
莱巴金娜 6-4 5-7 6-2 萨巴伦卡 · 赛后场上采访
Now, we'd like to invite our finalist,
下面 有请我们的亚军
Aryna Sabalenka, who put up a hell
萨巴伦卡 她打了一场
of a battle, up to the stage.
了不起的苦战 请上台
Aryna, we saw you just now speaking
萨巴伦卡 我们刚看到你
with your team.
在和团队说话
What did you say to them?
你对他们说了什么？
What did they say to you?
他们又对你说了什么？
Honestly, I don't know.
说实话 我不知道
We saw how much it means to you.
我们都看得出这对你的分量
That's the last thing I can I want
现在我最不想做的事
to do right now is give a speech,
就是站在这儿讲话
but I'll try my very best.
但我会尽力
Thank you everyone.
谢谢大家
Thank you
谢谢你们
for your support throughout two weeks.
这两周以来的支持
It was it was amazing playing in front
能在你们面前打球
of you all.
真的太好了
And obviously I'm disappointed, but I want
我当然很失望 但我想
to congratulate Elena on an incredible year,
恭喜莱巴金娜 这一年
on incredible results.
太出色 成绩也太出色
And well deserved.
实至名归
Enjoy it. Have fun tonight,
好好享受 今晚
tomorrow and till the end of the season
明天 一直玩到赛季结束
so I can play can win some titles.
这样我才能赢几个冠军
Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you all of the sponsors
谢谢所有赞助商
for making this event possible.
让这项赛事得以举办
And thank you I don't know everyone
还要谢谢 我也不知道
who helped me throughout this two weeks.
这两周帮过我的每个人
I really feel like home here
我在这儿真的像在家
and cannot wait to come back next year.
等不及明年再回来
Thank you to my team, to my friends.
谢谢我的团队 我的朋友
I wish I could perform
我真希望自己能
a little bit better.
打得再好一点
But I guess next year.
不过 那就明年吧
Thank you.
谢谢